Remember that in the chronology of the appearance of communication systems,
请记住，在通信系统出现的时间顺序中，
your digestive system is very precocious.
您的消化系统出现得非常早。
The first movement in the communication system is a fluidic, autocrine-type movement.
通信系统中的第一个运动是自分泌类型的流体运动。
In other words, I must learn to know myself.
换句话说，我必须学会认识自己。
Once I know myself, I can exchange.
一旦我认识了自己，我就可以进行交流。
And only then can I digest.
然后我才能消化。
Only afterwards will the connective, circulatory, endocrine system emerge.
只有在那之后，循环内分泌结缔组织系统才会出现。
Look at the system.
看看这个系统。
endocrine system, it is dependent on my circulatory system.
内分泌系统，它受我的循环系统的支配。
First, my enteric system appears, and only then the parasympathetic and then the orthosympathetic.
首先，我的
This means that my first brain is digestive. I was not first cerebralized,
肠道系统出现，然后才是副交感神经，再然后是交感神经。
I was first enteric, I was first digestive. Don't
这意味着
forget the five major phases.
我的第一个大脑是消化系统。我不是先被大脑化的，
Fertilization, gastrulation, neurulation, metamerization, and
我首先
delimitation.
是肠道的，我首先是消化的。不要
On the first day, I have an axis here that forms between my
忘记五个主要阶段。
two polar bodies.
受精、原肠胚形成、神经胚形成、分节和
This axis is very important because it is at the basis of my digestive development.
定界。
Each time I have a cell division or a cell cleavage,
第一天，我的
I have an increase in my metabolic system.
两个极体之间出现了一个轴。
metabolic. In other words, I have an increase in the cell membrane.
这个轴非常重要，因为它是我的消化系统发育的基础。
But each time I have this, I have a small loss of water.
每次我进行细胞分裂或细胞裂解时，
And so each time I have this continuous movement in this phase of development,
我的系统都会增加。
this power, it will cause the appearance of a cavity called here the blasto
代谢。换句话说，我的细胞膜增加了。
coel.
但每次发生这种情况，我都会损失一点水分。
Well, we can see here the first image of your
因此，每次我在这个发育阶段持续进行这种运动时，
digestive system.
这种力量将导致一个腔的出现，这里称为胚泡
cell.
细胞。
Eh  bien,  on  peut  voir  ici  la  première  image  de  votre  système
嗯，我们可以在这里看到您的消化系统的第一张图像。
digestif.
消化系统。
We can say this is the anlage.
我们可以说这是雏形。
of your vitelline cavity, which will ultimately be integrated into your digestive tract.
您的卵黄囊腔，它实际上将整合到您的消化道中。
And we observe that this cavity is never centered; it is always eccentric.
我们看到这个腔从未居中，它总是偏心的。
Why? Because it responds to the totality of polarity.
为什么？因为它响应了极性的整体性。
We see this blastocoel appearing, and we observe that the embryo here begins to organize itself.
我们看到这个胚泡出现，我们看到胚胎在这里开始组织起来。
Not only do I have an organization into micromeres, meaning small cells,
我不仅有微米级的组织，也就是说小细胞的组织，
where we see that I have a vegetal pole, a pole...
我们看到我有一个植物极，一个极...
swollen, an assimilative pole
膨胀的，一个同化极
a force, a potency
一种力量，一种能量
to seek out
去寻找
trophic information
营养信息
I have a cavity
我有一个腔体
which is the blastocoel
那就是胚泡腔
blastocoel means
胚泡腔的意思是
blastocoel
胚泡腔
the sky, the germ
天空，胚芽
of the sky
来自天空
at some point, I will seek the sky
我将在某个时刻寻找天空
that I must
我必须
integrate into an inner sky
融入一个内在的天空
that is to say, initially
也就是说，一开始
my digestive system is completely open to the exterior, and it will
我的消化系统完全向外开放，它将
gradually integrate itself
一点一点地整合
internally. This is why your digestive tract represents
到内部。这就是为什么你的消化道代表着
a quality we refer to as
我们称之为的一种品质
humus. I have humus within my digestive tract. This
腐殖质。我的消化道里有腐殖质。这种
humus can be compared to an intestinal flora.
腐殖质，我们可以将其比作肠道菌群
intestinal flora. Thus, the living quality of my intestine...
肠道菌群。所以我的肠道的生命品质...
represents the living quality of my 'terroir' in which I am
代表着我所处的这片土地的生命品质
nourished.
被滋养。
I am first on the outside, and the sky, in Chinese medicine we speak
我首先在外面，而天空，在中医中我们谈论
of that,
这个，
I reintegrate that internally.
我把它重新整合到内部。
The establishment of the vitelline cavity and the external coelom.
卵黄囊和外体腔的形成。
I am integrated into my uterine mucosa.
我被整合到我的子宫内膜中。
Here I have a tissue called the trophoblast, this black layer,
我这里有一个叫做滋养层的组织，这个黑色的层，
that is still a blast cell.
这仍然是一个胚泡细胞。
That is an amniotic cavity.
这是一个羊膜腔。
That means that I am forming in my developmental phase
这意味着我在我的发育阶段中构建自己
between fluid layers.
在液体层之间。
I am surrounded by fluids.
我被液体包围着。
I develop within these fluids.
我在这些液体中发育。
Between the two, I have a tissue that faces my primitive coelomic cavity.
两者之间，我有一个组织，它面向我的原始体腔。
This will be my digestive system.
这将是我的消化系统。
I have cells that face my amniotic cavity.
我有一些细胞面向我的羊膜腔。
This will be my ectodermal, cerebral tissue.
这将是我的外胚层组织，大脑。
You must understand that this is a process.
你必须明白这是一个过程。
growth organized by fulcrums by
通过支点组织的生长
the growth rate
生长速度
differential to now understand the establishment of
差异化，以便现在理解其建立
my vitelline
我的腔体
cavity and my external coelom, the part that is peripheral
卵黄囊和我的外部细胞体，即外围部分
here for the
这里，对于
black, it is placed in a trophic bath, this layer
黑色部分，它被置于营养浴中，这一层
here as it is in
这里，因为它在
the uterus, it is the first
子宫里，这是第一层
layer that receives nutritive information, so if I eat faster, I
接收营养信息的层，所以如果我吃得更快，我就会
grow faster, but
长得更快，但是
as the peripheral layer here grows very, very quickly, there is a tearing
由于这里的外围层生长得非常非常快，我感到一种撕裂
between my layer
在我的外围层和我的中心层之间，这种撕裂将形成一层细胞，我们称之为
we call the
赫塞尔膜，它保持着我们称之为
cavity here and I have the vitelline here
这里的腔体，我这里有速度
And this will give rise to what is called an extra-embryonic mesodermal reticulum.
这将形成我们所说的网状结构或中胚层，胚外
And this reticulum will grow in relation to my periphery.
-胚外。
Here, we see at a given moment that it tears here.
这个网状结构将相对于我的外围生长。
And this tearing will cause me to transition from a tissue that
在这里，我们看到在某个时刻它在这里撕裂了。
we call the blastocoel
这种撕裂将使我从一个我们称之为胚泡的组织
to a tissue now called the vitelline cavity and the extraembryonic coelom,
我们称之为胚泡的组织
another cavity.
到一个我们现在称之为卵黄囊和外部细胞体的组织，
It is in this tissue.
另一个腔体。
this phase that I will appear as a primitive, organized embryonic stalk.
它在这个组织中。
It was already there when I had my extra-primitive embryonic stalk, at the
在这个阶段，我将以原始胚胎柄的形式出现，有组织的。
moment of integration of the primitive embryo, at the moment of nidation (implantation), which is the
在我有我的胚外
first
-原始胚胎柄的时候，它就已经在那里了，在
contact with the mother, not yet organized.
原始胚胎整合的时候，在着床的时候，这是与母亲的
And it is this phase that will organize an S-shape within my
第一次
embryonic
接触，但尚未组织。
disc.
正是这个阶段将使我的胚胎
And here, there is a point
芽中形成一个S形。
of very important support that we have seen; not only do I have the organization of an embryonic stalk
胚胎芽。
and not only
这里有一个点。
I have a fulcrum between a dome of expansion and a dome of impaction within
我们看到一个非常重要的支撑点，我不仅有一个胚胎柄的组织，
the very tissue
而且
which is the anlage for the establishment of an axial process of my embryo. This
在我的组织中，在一个扩张穹顶和一个内陷穹顶之间有一个支撑点，
means
我的组织
that this phase here will lead us to this notochordal phase, a
是我的胚胎轴向过程形成的雏形。这意味着
veut  dire
这意味着
que  cette  phase  ici  va  nous  amener  à  cette  phase  notocordale,  une
这个阶段将使我们进入脊索阶段，一个
S-shape and this
S 形，这个
S-shape will induce a movement
S 形将带来一个运动，
which is also involved in what is called a permeation field,
这个运动也与我们所说的渗透场有关，
an infusion field and a permeation field
一个灌注场和一个渗透场，
which organizes the amniotic vesicle anteriorly and the vitelline vesicle posteriorly
它将羊膜囊组织向前，卵黄囊组织向后，
and which gives this particular S-shape to my embryo.
并赋予我的胚胎这种特殊的 S 形。
And if I have a fulcrum, the cells in the convergent part
如果我有一个支点，会聚部分的细胞
will grow faster than the cells in the, let's say, convex part.
会比凸部分的细胞生长得更快。
concave with a fulcrum here which is a fixed point, what was this point called?
凹面，这里有一个支点，它是一个固定点，这个点叫什么来着？
future cranial base, we call it point 0, it
未来的颅底，我们称之为 0 点，
is the anlage of what is called the primitive pure cranio-sacral axis,
它是我们所说的颅骶轴的雏形，
meaning I will find myself with a movement
纯粹的原始，这意味着我将发现自己处于一种运动中，
here, specific, organized
这里有特定的组织，
by acidic or basic fields
由酸性或碱性场组织。
We find two different pH types in my amniotic or vitelline cavity,
我的羊膜腔或卵黄腔中有两种不同的 pH 值，
with what is called a neuroenteric canal for the reorganization of my metabolic plan,
伴随着我们所说的神经肠管，它重新组织了我的代谢平面，
but at the same time, the embryo begins to take its shape here,
但与此同时，胚胎开始在这里形成它的形状，
with this developing axial process,
随着这个轴向过程的发展，
with synchronous phenomena,
伴随着同步现象，
which means that not only at the moment I have this level,
这意味着，不仅在我达到这个水平的时候，
I have the complete rupture of my asymmetry,
我的不对称性完全破裂了，
but I have a very important axial process developing.
而且一个非常重要的轴向过程正在发展。
This axial process...
这个轴向过程...
here, notochordal, is at the base of the global development of
这里，脊索是我的胚胎整体发育的基础。
my embryo.
我的胚胎。
And we saw that this axial process was an organizing center for the entirety of my embryo,
我们已经看到，这个轴向过程是我整个胚胎的组织中心，
that it was organized with a fulcrum we called the cranial base and the notochordal axis,
它与我们称之为颅底和脊索轴的支点一起组织，
down to my sacrum, and that between the two, I would find myself on an umbilical plane.
直到我的骶骨，在这两者之间，我将处于脐平面上。
So we could almost say that I develop between my umbilicus and my
所以我们几乎可以说，我是在我的肚脐和我的
umbilicus.
肚脐之间发育的。
base of the skull. My heart, which will give rise to my diaphragm and my liver. There
颅底。我的心脏将形成我的膈肌和我的肝脏。
is an
我的发育中存在一种智慧。就好像有人告诉你那是一个
an invagination. But if we see it
内陷。但如果我们从整体和生长来看，它是一个
in its entirety and in its growth, it is
从整体和生长来看，它是一个
an evagination. What does that change? It changes my fulcrum. If it
外翻。这有什么改变？它改变了我的支点。如果它是一个
were an
如果它是一个
invagination, my sacrum would be the fixed point.
内陷，那么我的骶骨将是固定点。
But ultimately, the sacrum becomes a mobile fulcrum like my sternum.
但最终，骶骨变成了像我的胸骨一样的可移动支点。
So my true fulcrum is to bring my sacrum back into its
所以我的真正支点是把我的骶骨带回它的位置。
embryonic fulcrum
fulcrum  embryonnaire
to restore its primary function of reorganization.
pour lui redonner sa fonction primaire de réorganisation.
Because at that moment, different functions will develop.
Parce qu'à ce moment-là, j'ai différentes fonctions qui vont se développer.
There are superimpositions.
J'ai des superpositions.
Not only do I have an axial process, thus truly a primitive cranio-sacral axis,
Non seulement j'ai un processus axiel, donc vraiment un axe crânio-sacré primitif,
Furthermore, at the same moment, there is a break in symmetry.
En plus, au même moment, j'ai une rupture de la symétrie.
That is to say, I have a nodal flow which changes the molecular aspect of my embryo
C'est-à-dire que j'ai un flux nodal qui change l'aspect moléculaire de mon embryon
on an electrical plane, which causes morphogenic particles to develop alongside.
sur un plan électrique, qui fait que j'ai des particules morphogènes qui vont se développer à côté.
And so, in this movement, all the genomic organization develops.
Et donc, dans ce mouvement, j'ai toute l'organisation génomique qui se développe.
So, if I restore an embryonic fulcrum, the body knows how to reorganize itself.
Donc, si je redonne un fulcrum embryonnaire, le corps, il sait comment se réorganiser.
First, the notochord.
D'abord, l'ombrine.
And then, the sphenobasilar.
Et puis, le phénobasilaire.
Then, the heart.
Puis, le cœur.
then the diaphragm, then the liver, then the adrenals, then the gonads.
puis  le  diaphragme,  puis  le  foie,  puis  les  surrénales,  puis  les  gonadiques.
In fact, what is my sacrum?
En fait, mon sacrum, c'est quoi ?
But it is the base of the skull.
Mais c'est la base du crâne.
I cannot separate them.
Je ne peux pas les séparer.
This level is my embryonic fulcrum.
Ce  niveau -ci  est  mon  fulcrum  embryonnaire.
Why? Because at that moment,
Pourquoi ? Parce qu'à ce moment-là,
the future base of the skull and the sacrum are one.
la future base du crâne et le sacrum font un.
This is...
Ça, c'est...
a functional unit, in fact. It must be understood in terms of its function. I
unité  fonctionnelle  en  fait.  Il  faut  le  comprendre  dans  sa  fonction.  J
therefore have a flat basal tissue,
'ai  donc  un  tissu  de  base  plat,
throughout this developmental movement, a cavity develops
par  tout  ce  mouvement  développemental,  il  y  a  une  cavité  qui  se  développe
anteriorly like this,
vers  l 'avant  comme  ceci,
and this vitelline vesicle that develops posteriorly. But also intrinsic qualities,
et  cette  vésicule  viteline  qui  se  développe  vers  l 'arrière.  Mais  aussi  des  qualités  intrinsèques,
which causes me to transition from an S-shaped system. The cells
qui  fait  que  je  passe  d 'un  système  en  forme  de  S.  Les  cellules
that are in order,
qui  sont  en  ordre,
in relation to my anterior dome,
en regard de mon dôme vers l'avant,
will develop much faster than the cells that are posterior.
vont se développer beaucoup plus vite que les cellules qui sont en arrière.
Consequently, globally,
Ce qui fait que globalement,
if I now look at the structure in its entirety,
si je regarde maintenant juste le verre dans sa globalité,
in growth, I observe this,
dans la croissance, je constate ceci,
that I have a point of global non-growth.
que j'ai un point de non-croissance globale.
There will be this development of this base.
Il va y avoir ce développement de cette base.
And there, what do I have?
Et là, qu'est-ce que j'ai ?
I have a fulcrum, which we call the future cranial base.
J'ai un point d'appui qu'on appelle la future base.
cranium, that is to say, it is the tip of the notochord; on both sides, I
crâne  c 'est  à  dire  c 'est  la  pointe  de  manotocorte  de  part  et  d 'autres  j
have the paraxial cartilage,
'ai  le  cartilage  paraxial
the hypophyseal cartilage, and what will become the
le  cartilage  hypophysaire  et  qu 'est  ce  que  va  devenir  le
hypophyseal cartilage and the
垂体软骨和软骨
paraxial cartilage, the occipital system and the sphenoidal system which
轴旁枕骨系统和蝶骨系统，它
is organized with a point
以一个尖端组织起来
of support, which is a global fulcrum, what we refer to as a fulcrum.
支撑点，这是一个整体的支撑点，我们称之为支撑点
A fixed, relative point, if you will, which becomes,
一个固定的、相对的点，如果你愿意，它会
afterwards, gradually, the area where what we call
之后，逐渐成为我们所说的
the occipito-sphenoidal system, here, which
枕蝶系统，在这里，它
is the result of this developmental movement.
是这种发展运动的结果。
You see, when I take my sacrum here—this is what we did—I connect to its embryonic fulcrum,
你看，当我拿起我的骶骨时，这就是我们所做的，我连接到它的胚胎支点
that is to say, I connect, ultimately, to...
也就是说，我最终连接到……
at its point, what I call the image
到它的点，我称之为“道”的
of the Tao, you see.
形象，你看。
Here, I have a point, here,
在这里，我有一个点，在这里，
where the tissue here is in hyperactivity,
这里的组织处于过度活跃状态，
in hypoactivity, so I have
或低活跃状态，所以我有一个
a fulcrum
支撑点
between two movements, what
在两个运动之间，我称之为
I call the pre-morphogenetic
前形态发生
force,
力，
which does not yet have form or structure,
它还没有形状、结构，
but which contains its potential,
但它包含着它的潜力，
and already at this level
并且已经在这个层面上
on a sacral and occipital plane.
在骶骨和枕骨平面上。
As soon as I have this fulcrum, the body knows what it must do since it has its organizational plan.
一旦我有了这个支撑点，身体就知道它该做什么，因为它有它的组织计划。
This is one of the first things it does in its form.
这是它形成的第一件事。
This form gives this axis.
这种形式给出了这个轴。
I take my sacrum, and here I have a primitive notochordal axis.
我拿起我的骶骨，这里有一个原始的脊索轴。
Then there will be a regression of the structure, but not of its function.
然后结构会退化，但我的功能不会。
Its function is always there, because it is primitive.
我的功能总是在那里，因为它是原始的。
It organizes a structure at the occipital level.
它在枕骨层面组织了一个结构。
Sometimes there are people where it is deviated. They have false fulcrums. They
有时有些人会偏离。他们有错误的支点。他们
have false fulcrums.
有错误的支撑点。
That's why I say one must learn to work with health. Because
这就是为什么我说我们必须学会与健康合作。因为
this is health.
这就是健康。
It is always there. Initially, it is a dense field, and
它总是在那里。最初它是一个致密的场，然后
then during growth, it will regress.
在生长过程中它会退化。
This means that the notochord, what is the vestige of the notochord? It is my nucleus pulposus.
这意味着脊索，脊索的遗迹是什么？是我的髓核。
Okay, so a kind of regression in the tissue, but the axis is given by
好的，所以在组织中有一种退化，但轴是由
at that moment we will
那一刻，我们将
see that this is what we call the midline, three midlines that we call
看到这被称为中线，我们称之为三条中线
the notochordal midline, the neuronal midline, and the midline we had studied
脊索中线、神经中线以及我们研究过的中线
last time, the anterior digestive midline; we also see what
上次是前消化道中线，我们还看到了
we call
所谓的
the linea alba, it's called the white line in a pregnant woman
白线，在孕妇身上被称为白线
we still see this line appearing, which is the fusion line on the testicles.
我们仍然可以看到这条线出现，它是睾丸的闭合线。
We see the scrotum in women, we still clearly see the line.
我们看到女性的阴囊，我们仍然能清楚地看到这条线。
If you look at the palate, you see all these axes.
如果你看上颚，你会看到所有这些轴线。
Bruno Cicli adds a fourth, which is an electrical field,
布鲁诺·西克利又增加了一个第四个，即电场，
whose vital point will be found at the level of the hara.
其生命点将位于丹田。
More precisely, because it's still umbilical,
更精确地说，因为它仍然是脐部的，
but if we look, there is a vascular remnant
但如果我们观察，会有一个血管残迹
which will be found, what we call a diverticulum,
它将形成一个所谓的憩室，
organized by my...
由我的...
omphalomesenteric plane, that is, the superior mesenteric artery.
卵黄肠系膜平面组织，即肠系膜上动脉。
Not only do I have a rupture of my asymmetry, but I also have, during that moment, the
我不仅不对称性被打破，而且在此期间，我的
establishment of my third tissue, what we call pure mesodermal tissue.
第三种组织，即所谓的纯中胚层组织，也正在形成。
I have my notochordal axis, I have the axis, what we call the primitive streak,
我有我的脊索轴，我有我的轴，也就是所谓的原条，
and the
以及
first impulse of the movement of my original tissue.
我的原始组织运动的第一个冲动。
epithelial is a tissue that will first organize my endoderm
上皮组织是一种首先组织我的内胚层的组织
so that means
所以这意味着
that my ectoderm or what I call the primitive epiblast of
我的外胚层，或者我称之为原始外胚层
type
外胚层类型将通过这条原始线和我的
ectodermal type will already influence through this primitive streak and through my
轴向过程影响我的消化系统组织，然后
axial process my digestive system in its organization, then
我将拥有我的中胚层，首先是原发的电场
after I will
我们都来自一个细胞。我们都来自哪种类型的细胞？我们都来自
have my mesoderm, what is primarily an electrical field
一个上皮细胞。不是中胚层细胞。这是一个发育运动。
We all come from one cell. And what type of cell do we all come from? We all come
只是为了肝脏。但我不能把它从它的背景中分离出来。我的胚胎有一个弯曲运动
from an epithelial cell. Not mesodermal. It's a developmental movement.
我的胚胎的弯曲运动将把心脏带到
Just for the liver. But I cannot separate it from its context. I have a flexion movement
它的位置。
of my embryo. The flexion movement of my embryo will bring the heart to
这将产生压力。
its place.
在卵黄囊上部，上部。
This will create a pressure
它将整合我前脊索板之外的细胞
on the superior vitelline vesicle, superior part.
形成一个空间，将心脏部分与
This will integrate cells that are beyond my precardial plate
腹膜部分分隔开来。
to form a space that will delimit the cardiac part from
这种划分会产生什么？
the peritoneal part.
它将产生我们称之为原始膈肌，即横膈膜。
And what will this delimitation create?
信息流总是存在的。
And this time,
而这一次，
it arrives in a different compartment.
它进入了一个不同的隔间。
So the flow of trophic information, the torrent of water that arrives,
因此，营养信息的流动，即涌入的水流，
will begin to congest under the diaphragm.
将开始在膈肌下方充血。
And this space of congestion, on a mesodermal plane,
而这个充血区域，在间充质层面，
in relation with the endodermal level, will create a first anlage that we call the liver.
与外胚层相关，将形成我们称之为肝脏的第一个雏形。
But the embryo has grown.
但胚胎已经长大。
And at a given moment, my liver, through vascular fields that will modify,
在某个时刻，我的肝脏，通过血管场的改变，
It will grow towards the right. It will not turn towards the
它会向右生长。它不会向
right.
右旋转。
It will grow towards the right. And these are the embryonic movements.
它会向右生长。这就是胚胎运动。
I do... I can develop in that direction, you see.
我做... 我可以向那边发展，你明白吗。
I have the space, like the heart, at a given moment, it is said to go towards the left.
我有空间，就像心脏一样，在某个时刻，我们说它向左。
No, it can develop in that direction. It grows in that direction.
不，它可以向那边发展。它向那边生长。
So that means that my embryonic movements are movements of development
所以这意味着我的胚胎运动是发展运动。
in a growth phase. These are the internal forces of
在生长阶段。这是内部的
expansion. These are the arteries,
扩张力。是动脉，
it's the vascular movements that decide. We organize around your fluidic field.
是血管运动决定了。我们围绕着你的流体场组织起来。
And around what does your fluidic field organize itself? Your electrical field. And where does that come from?
你的流体场是围绕什么组织的？你的电场。这又从何而来
?
？
Ultimately from the void. So, ultimately, I organize myself within chaos. It is there that this notochordal
最终来自虚空。所以最终我在混沌中组织起来。正是这个脊索
will
将
provide the impetus for the neural plate.
为神经板提供冲动。
I have neural tissue here above, like this,
我这里上面有一块神经组织，像这样，
which is there, everything is fine.
它在那里，一切都很好。
And then suddenly, a notochordal axis arrives underneath.
然后突然，下面出现了一个脊索轴。
A well-axialized structure.
一个轴向很好的东西。
There are metabolic movements.
存在代谢运动。
Imagine that the ceiling here is my neural plate.
你们想象一下，这里的天花板是我的神经板。
And here, I have my notochord.
而这里，我有我的脊索。
In the void here, like this, which is there.
在虚空中，像这样，它在那里。
The cells that are right there have their growth slowed.
就在那里的细胞，它们的生长速度减慢了。
They are inhibited.
被抑制了。
I have the primitive ectoderm here.
我这里有原始外胚层。
I have my notochord
我有我的脊索
which carries information
它有一个信息
here, with a deceleration
在这里，伴随着减速
this time, again, these are differential growth rates,
这一次，再次，这是生长速度的
it's the same
差异，这是相同的
algorithm, which causes the area
算法，使得该区域
that is here, does not grow at the same rate,
在这里，我没有以相同的速度成长
whereas here,
但在这里，
I begin to form what is called a groove,
我开始形成一个所谓的凹槽
you see,
你看到了吗
and this groove here, like this,
而这个凹槽在这里，就像这样
changes the compartment
改变了隔间
here. And what will that change? It will change a vascular system.
在这里。那它会改变什么呢？它会改变一个血管系统。
That is to say,
也就是说
that I have a vascular trajectory organizing itself. And I resume my algorithm
我有一个正在形成的血管轨迹。我回到我的算法
point of origin.
的起点。
The mesodermal tissue, the internal tissue, does not grow at the same rate
中胚层组织，内部组织，没有以相同的速度生长
and becomes
并成为
a motor because it brings trophic information, it nourishes the cells. But
一个引擎，因为它带来了营养信息，它滋养细胞。但是
the
这个
tube does not grow at the same rate. It slows down.
管道没有以相同的速度生长。它减慢了。
Above, as I eat thoroughly, I become obese.
在上面，因为我吃得很多，我变得肥胖。
I develop and I coil.
我发展并卷曲。
And this is how the process of
这就是
the posterior midline will develop.
后正中线
If I take a vascular field
如果我在这里取一个原始的
here primitive,
血管场，
and if I place behind my embryo here, which is like this, let's say, my
然后我把我的胚胎放在这里，它是这样的，我们可以说，我的
neural tube,
神经管，
this is what happens.
这就是发生的事情。
growth that occurs like this with a
生长是这样发生的，最终
coiling finally around my cardiac region which
围绕着我的心脏区域
comes
卷曲，它
to push on the vitelline vesicle, the superior part here of my vesicle which
推动卵黄囊的上部，在这里，我的卵黄囊将
will create the septum transversum
形成横膈膜
here the continuous flow of information that arrives here that is processed
这里是持续的信息流，我们在这里管理
so we can say that cerebralization
所以我们可以说脑化
which leads to cardialization, which leads to diaphragmatization, which leads to
导致心脏化，导致膈化，导致
hepatization.
肝化。
Afterwards, there will be a pulmonary space, so there is pneumatization,
之后，将有一个肺部空间，因此有一个气化，
which will open a space between the posterior part and
它将在后部和
the liver, which will create adrenalization.
肝脏之间打开一个空间，这将导致肾上腺化。
To have the organization and definitive establishment of my gonads, I need my adrenal glands.
为了使我的性腺组织和最终定位，我需要我的肾上腺。
And my kidneys.
和我的肾脏。
So we see here that the notochord initially regresses.
所以我们在这里看到脊索最初消失了。
from the anlage of the neurohypophysis of the diencephalic floor,
来自间脑底部的神经垂体原基，
future cranial base.
未来的颅底。
It is the developmental movement of the notochordal process
这是脊索过程的发育运动，
which will enable the future development
它将允许未来的发展
of my cranial base and my sacrum.
我的颅底和骶骨。
Whereas up to the cloacal membrane,
而直到泄殖腔膜，
future developmental space for the sacrum.
骶骨未来的发育空间。
It is a notochord that will establish itself there,
脊索会出现在那里，
which is coincidentally at the tip of the rectouterine pouch (pouch of Douglas).
它碰巧在道格拉斯陷凹的尖端。
the terminal part of my peritoneum.
我的腹膜的末端部分。
We see here, you see, the entire primitive notochordal axis
我们在这里看到，你看，整个原始脊索轴
with my cranial base and my sacrum.
与我的颅底和骶骨。
We see here, you see, my notochord
我们在这里看到，你看，我的脊索
up to the level of my cranial base.
直到我的颅底。
We see again here my notochordal process
我们再次在这里看到我的脊索过程
You see, the tip of what is called the rectouterine pouch (pouch of Douglas),
你看，我们称之为道格拉斯陷凹的尖端，
the terminal part,
末端部分，
with my notochord the flexion of the embryo well
随着我的脊索，胚胎的弯曲，很好地
to understand this fluidic dynamic we clearly see
理解这种流体动力学，我们清楚地看到
here the coiling of the embryo's development, the elongation, the growth
这里是胚胎发育的卷曲、伸长和生长，
but look closely
但请仔细看，
how my vascular system becomes a fulcrum, you see the approximation of my tubes
我的血管系统如何成为一个支点，你看我的管子靠得很近，
endocardial here because they don't progress at the same speed, in fact the error in this drawing is that
心内膜在这里，因为它们实际上没有以相同的速度移动，这个图中的错误是
we
我们
close, God of me
我的天啊
neural tube, I have the integration of the pharyngeal gut, for example, in the part
神经管，例如，我在尾部整合了咽肠，
caudal
尾部
and I have at the same time the closure of my neural tube. So on the first 28th day, I
同时我的神经管也闭合了。所以在第28天，我
have
我
the integration of my external coelom into an internal coelom, and I have the integration of
将我的外体腔整合为内体腔，并将
my neural tube into an internal neural tube. This means that for the first time, I have
我的神经管整合为内神经管。这意味着我第一次
a fulcrum at a cerebrospinal fluid level that I have integrated
在脑脊液水平上有一个支点，我已经将其整合
into
在
its first personality.
它的第一个个性。
I start from my embryonic pedicle and return to
我从我的胚胎柄出发，然后回到
my embryonic pedicle.
我的胚胎柄。
I perform the movement for myself of Umaï Rémaï's development.
我为自己做了Umaï Remaï的发展运动。
You have found it.
你找到了。
Perhaps it was there in its function; now it becomes there in its structure.
也许它在那里发挥作用，现在它在那里形成结构。
So, what is important to conceive is that I coil around
所以，重要的是要理解，我围绕着
my vascular plane.
我的血管平面盘绕。
That's why one must always bring the fluids back towards the center.
这就是为什么我们总是需要将液体引向中心。
to have in the development of my circulatory system, that ultimately
在我的循环系统发育过程中，最终
it starts from the
它从
periphery towards the center. I must coalesce.
外围向中心发展。我必须聚集起来。
I immerse myself in the tissue fluid. I immerse myself in my
我潜入组织的液体中。我潜入我的
tissue. I swim a bit at first. When I find a movement, I
组织中。一开始我有点像在游泳。当我找到一个运动时，我
find a fulcrum, a point
找到一个支点，一个
of balance. I stabilize. Afterwards, analyze the tissue.
平衡点。我固定住。然后，分析组织。
And there you enter into Becker's tissue history; there you enter into the memory.
然后你就进入了贝克尔的组织故事，你就进入了记忆。
But you must touch the tissue where it wants to be recognized, and not where you want
但你必须触碰组织愿意被识别的地方，而不是你想要
to recognize it.
识别它的地方。
First thing, I listen to its movement; once I find its fulcrum, its point of balance,
首先，我倾听它的运动，一旦我找到它的全息点，它的平衡点，
and there I enter into its history; at a given moment I pass, I enter, I merge,
然后我进入它的故事，在某个时刻我穿过，我进入，我融合，
and the tissue will give you an image,
然后组织会给你一个图像，
a word that can come from afar, you know, what is it?
一个可能来自远方的词，嗯，那是什么？
either on an embryonic point or even, for some, have
要么在一个胚胎点上，甚至，对于某些人来说，拥有
the transgenerational capacity.
跨代的能力。